Hey.
Hi.
What are you doing?
Well, you know, I was thinking
of moving the couch over here.
Why would you want
to do that?
So that there would be
a decent place for me to sit.
Rach...
There is a decent place...
And your lap does not count.
Okay, come on,
help me move this.
No, no, no.
No?
No. Rosita does not move.
I'm sorry.
Rosita?
As in...?
As in Rosita does not move.
Joey, it's
just a chair.
What's the big deal?
The big deal is that
it is the exact equal distance
from the bathroom to the kitchen
and it's at the perfect angle
so you don't get any glare
coming off of Stevie.
Stevie the TV?
Is there a problem?
No.
Oh, what does he know?
Come on, Rosita.
Us chicas got
to stick together.
( grunting )
Oh!
( gasps )
You bitch.
[Captioning sponsored by
WARNER BROS. TELEVISION]
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, Ross, so, I was
checking out
the real estate
section...
Yeah?
Look at this.
It looks like
Mom and Dad's house.
It even has a tree
with a broken
limb out front.
And the, uh...
the window
in the attic...
Oh, my God!
What? What happened
to the window
in the attic?
I can't believe Mom and Dad
are selling the house.
I can't believe
they didn't even tell us.
I can't believe I still
don't know what happened
to the window
in the attic.
Okay, come on, Joey
I'll buy you a new one, all
right?
We'll go down
to the store
right now
and we'll get you
a new chair.
She's not even cold yet.
But don't you think Rosita would
have wanted you to move on?
I mean, she did always put
your comfort first.
Well, that's true.
I can't believe we have
to say good-bye
to the house
we grew up in.
Man, some stranger's going
to be living in my room.
Well, after 15 years
of Mom and Dad keeping
it as a shrine to you
it's time the
velvet ropes came down.
They kept your room for awhile.
Oh, please.
Dad turned my room
into a gym
20 minutes after
I moved out.
I got to say,
a tanning bed
and a stack of
Victoria's Secret catalogs--
not a gym.
Come on.
You know
they love you.
As much as
they love you?
I was their firstborn.
They thought she was barren.
It's not my fault.
I hate this year.
What's wrong
with this year?
Well, okay, it's
already February
and I've only given
two massages
and they were both
the worst tippers in the world.
That was me and Ross.
Oh, that's right.
Hey, you know, if you want
to pick up some extra cash
some friends of mine
made good money in college
doing telemarketing.
Yeah, and it'll probably
be better
than the last
telephone job I had.
I probably won't have
to say "spank" as much.
What?
Oh, yeah, like you never called.
So, basically
this is very easy.
You read from
the script
and you try to sell
as much toner
as you possibly can.
Okay, I can do that.
Oh, by the way,
I love my office.
Why don't we do
a trial run.
Oh, okay.
Um... all right.
Hi, this is Phoebe
from Empire Office Supplies.
Can I speak to your
supply manager, please?
I'm the supply manager.
Okay, I'd like to talk to you
about your toner needs.
We don't need any toner.
Oh, okay, well, I'm sorry
to bother you. Bye-bye.
Yeah, you're right,
this is easy.
Okay, what was wrong
with that call?
Oh, well, all right.
Um, no offense,
but you were kind of rude.
They're always going to tell you
they don't need toner
but that's okay.
Because whatever they say,
you can find the answer to it
here in
the script.
Oh.
So I think you're
ready to sell toner.
Any last questions?
No.
Oh, wait, yes, I do.
I do have one question.
What is toner?
Joey.
Joe?
Full bag?
Beer's still cold.
Something terrible must
have happened here.
Oh, no, no, no, no...
Stevie, I was never here.
ROSS:
Dad?
I'm here.
Hey.
Hi.
God, it seems like
just yesterday
you guys used to come out
to watch me work.
Dad, we can't believe
you're selling the house.
Well, it's time for a new family
to start their memories here.
And hopefully,
their check will clear
before they find the crack
in the foundation
and the asbestos in the ceiling.
Let's just grab
our stuff--
get the hell
out of here.
I'm sorry we can't store
your childhood things anymore.
I can't wait to see
everything again.
All the memories.
I don't know what's
in the boxes down here
but I do know there are six
or seven Easy Bake Ovens
in the attic.
I used to love
to play "restaurant."
Not as much as you loved
to play "uncooked batter eater."
Hey, it is unreasonable
to expect a child
to wait for a light bulb
to cook brownies.
So, I think your boxes
are over here.
Oh, great.
Hey, Dad,
whose cigarettes are these?
I don't know.
They... they must
be your mother's.
But please, please
don't ask her.
I'll throw these away.
Cool, Dad!
My report cards!
Hey, check
this out, Dad...
Math, "A," Science, "A"
History, "A," Gym...
Ooh, my rock polisher!
Uh-oh.
What?
You know how the garage
floods every spring?
How are you ever
going to sell this place?
I think I accidentally
used Monica's boxes
to keep the water away
from the Porsche.
Oh, no, Dad.
Dad...
What the...?
Oh... Everything's ruined.
Dad, she's going
to be crushed.
You don't secretly smoke,
do you?
No.
So it's just your mother then.
Hi.
This is Phoebe from
Empire Office Supplies.
Can I speak to your
supply manager, please?
Earl. Thanks.
Hi, Earl.
This is Phoebe from
Empire Office Supplies.
I'd like to talk to you
about your toner needs.
( speaking in monotone ):
I don't need any toner.
I'm hearing what you're saying
but at our prices,
everyone needs toner.
Not me.
May I ask why?
You want to know why...
You want to know why?
I surely do.
Okay.
I don't need any toner...
because I'm going
to kill myself.
Um...
Is-is that because
you're out of toner?
Okay, so... no toner today.
Thanks, anyway. Bye-bye.
No! No! Wait! Wait!
I can't just let you
hang up.
Just... please talk to me.
Well...
I only had one thing
to do today.
Guess I could push it back.
Yeah. Now...
why do you want
to kill yourself?
I've been working
for ten years now
at this meaningless,
dead-end job
and nobody here
even knows that I exist.
Chandler?
I'm-I'm sorry?
No.
Oh... look...
I'm-I'm sure that people
know you exist.
Oh, yeah?
I work in a cubicle
surrounded
by people.
I've been
talking to you
for five minutes now
about killing myself...
and no one's even looked up
from their desk.
Hang on.
Hey, everybody, uh...
I'm going to kill myself.
I got nothing.
Good chair.
Now, if anybody asks,
your name is Rosita.
RACHEL:
Joey, you're going
to like it.
JOEY:
No, I won't.
How do you
even know?
I know what I like
and what I don't like
and it's not
the same chair.
Joey, you didn't
even sit in it.
I'm telling you,
it's such a nice chair.
I feel bad
sitting in it so soon.
Poor thing.
Cut down in
her prime.
Joey, the new chair
will be here in an hour.
Maybe we should actually move
Rosita out of here, you know?
Start the healing process?
Yeah, I guess
you're right.
She's healed!
That's weird.
No, it's not weird,
it's a miracle!
It's not a miracle,
Joey.
I'm sure there's
some explanation.
Oh, there is.
If you want
something enough
and your heart is pure,
wondrous things can happen!
Well, she'll
understand, right?
It's not like I
did it on purpose.
Dad, that won't
matter to her.
Look, all my stuff
is safe and dry
and all her stuff is-is...
is growing new stuff.
See, this is exactly
the kind of thing
that makes her think
you guys love me
more than you love her.
Oh, my God! Does she
really think that?
Well, can you blame her?
Well, I don't know.
I-I suppose we may
have favored you
unconsciously.
You were a
medical marvel!
The doctors said your
mother could never...
Dad, Dad, I don't want
to hear about it.
Really?
Well, not right now.
Okay, look-- Monica came here
for some memories
and, damn it, we're
going to give her some!
Okay, grab...
Grab some empty
boxes, okay?
We'll-we'll take
stuff from mine
and whatever we
can pass off as hers
we'll-we'll put
them in there.
Great.
Like, uh...
you know, like this.
This-- she could've
made this, right?
Sure.
And this, she-she
could've won this.
This could've
been hers.
Sure.
You know, if you
want to tell the
medical marvel
story while we work,
that'd be fine.
Oh! I am so psyched
I kept this chair
for myself!
Oh!
Yeah, me, too.
Wow!
You know that this thing
has speakers
in the headrest?
No. Really?
Yeah!
You can hook it up to your TV,
and you get radio.
My chair heals itself.
All right, so, Earl
let's just forget about
the people at the office, okay?
There-there's got to be
someone else in your life
that's worth
sticking around for.
What about... what about
your family or friends
or maybe a girlfriend?
( laughing ):
Yeah. Right.
Oh, sorry. Boyfriend.
Okay, I should...
I should probably
be getting back to my thing now.
See you.
No...
I'm not finished yet!
Don't you dare hang up on me!
The new girl's good.
Okay, so, which boxes
are mine?
Oh, these are
yours right here.
Okay.
Oh! A coloring book!
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, you loved
that thing.
You always had it
with you.
You never went anywhere
without that coloring book.
Really? Wow.
Looks like I had some trouble
staying inside the lines.
Nuh-uh!
Wow, look at this!
I can't believe I even
fit into this shirt.
Oh...
This is yours.
I don't know
how that got in there.
( nervous chuckle )
Hey, this...
this isn't
my stuff.
Ross, these are your boxes.
Where are my boxes?
Well, the garage flooded,
sweetie
and it ruined everything
in your boxes.
I'm sorry.
Just mine?
I'm afraid so.
So why... why wasn't
Ross's stuff ruined?
I used your boxes to divert
water away from the Porsche.
So, wait-- Ross's stuff is fine,
but I have no memories
because you wanted to keep
the bottom two inches
of your car away from water?
There was also leaves
and gook and stuff.
I can't believe this!
Screw it.
I'm having one.
Hey, Chandler.
Hey.
How would you like to sit
in a chair that fully reclines
has a rolling massage,
and speakers in the headrest?
Yeah, I'd love to
but I've tried that
so many times
they won't even let me
in the store anymore.
Well, what if I told you
that you could do it
in my apartment?
Are you telling me
that you bought the chair
that is making all other
lounge systems obsolete
the chair that Sit Magazine
called, "Chair of the Year"?
Mm-hmm.
I just purchased
the La-Z-Boy Ecliner 3000.
But that's awesome.
That's great.
What made you do it?
Well, it's a long story,
but, um, I broke Joey's chair.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You broke Joey's chair?
Yeah.
I thought I broke
Joey's chair.
That's why I replaced it
with mine.
Oh...
that's how it got fixed.
Well, what did you think
that-that elves came in
and fixed it?
No...
( laughs )
angels.
I'm getting my chair back.
Wha... w... hey.
Well, looks like
it wasn't healed after all.
Yeah.
So...
I guess this chair's mine now.
( clears throat )
( sighs pleasurably )
Joey, you broke my chair!
Your chair?
Yeah, he thought he broke
your chair
so he switched the chairs.
So, there was no miracle?
No, Joe, no miracle.
Oh, no, this is devastating.
My faith is shaken.
I'm so glad I have the new chair
to get me
through this difficult time
in my life.
Excuse me, could you tell me
where I could find Earl?
He's the supply manager here.
Sorry,
I don't know any Earl.
I'm right here!
Earl...
I'm Phoebe.
Phoebe?
The lady who sells toner?
Look, you can't kill yourself.
Look, um... I really appreciate
you coming down...
No-no, I can't...
I can't let you do it.
Why?
Because it was fate
that made me call you today.
I thought it was toner.
No.
Think about it, okay?
This isn't even
my regular job, okay?
And my first day on the job,
you're my first call
an-and somebody else
might've hung up on you
but I wouldn't do that,
because I know about this stuff.
My mom killed herself.
Really?
Yes.
How?
I'm not going to give you tips.
Look, don't you see?
Th-This-This...
this all came together
so that I could stop you
from doing this.
Couldn't it just
be a coincidence?
No, it's fate.
That doesn't really seem
like enough to be fate.
Oh, well... um, okay,
here's a weird thing--
my mother was also
a supply manager.
Well, I'm actually
the office manager.
Oh, my God, so was she!
And, get this, okay?
Your-Your name is Earl, right?
Her name was Pearl, Puh-earl.
W-Was there anything else?
Sure.
Um...
where you from?
Philadelphia.
Oh, my God!
So was she!
( laughing )
So, I've got goose...
I've got goose bumps.
( chuckling ):
Really?
Well, you know,
I'm wearing layers
and it's warm, so...
Yeah, yeah.
But it... look...
Okay, these jerks might not care
about you
but the universe does
and that says a lot.
Did you hear that?
I don't need you guys
to care about me
because the
universe cares!
The whole universe!
( laughing tauntingly )
I really wish they'd care
just a little bit, though.
Oh, this is terrible.
Everything is destroyed.
Look at this.
It obviously meant enough
for me to save it
and I don't even know
what it is.
Oh... it's still soft.
What do you think
this is?
Mon, I-I think
it was a mouse.
( screams )
( thuds )
Oh! Oh, my God!
How are you, honey?
MONICA:
How do you think
I am?
You've wrecked
all my childhood memories...
you love Ross
more than me...
and I just rubbed a dead mouse
on my face.
Sweetheart, we love you
just as much as Ross.
Now, I'm sorry about
everything that happened
and I'll probably
never be able to
make it up to you
but... here's a start.
What's this?
It's the key
to my Porsche.
Well... the key
to your Porsche.
What?
What?!
I've been thinking
of getting rid of it
and I was driving
it the other day
and I saw my reflection
in a store window.
Your mother's right--
I do look like an ass.
You're giving me
your Porsche?
You're kidding me, right?
W-W-Wai...
W-Wai-Wait a minute.
I mean, a couple of
stupid boxes get wet
and she gets a Porsche?!
Why don't we take
it for a spin?
All right!
Wh-What about me?!
I'm a medical marvel!
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
Oh, yeah.
( both sighing pleasurably )
Hey, guys.
BOTH:
Hey.
Do you know what happened
to Chandler's Barcalounger?
Oh, yeah, Joey broke it.
He had to get rid of it.
Are you kidding?
I get a Porsche
and the Barcalounger's gone?
This is the best day ever!